let's look at the solution to our
multi-predictor quiz where we have a
program for which the two-bit predictor
works for many instructions
p-share
covers some additional instructions and
g-share covers the rest that p-share
doesn't cover
but all of them can correctly predict
the same branches that the 2-bit
predictor can
so because the 2-bit predictor covers
the most branches and it's the cheapest
predictor what we want to do
is
use the 2-bit predictor for most of the
branches
so the correct answer here is e
hierarchical predictor
that chooses between
a 2-bit predictor
and a
predictor that combines the patient and
g-share
so what this first part does is it
basically makes most of the branches
just go to the two-bit predictor so that
the space in the more expensive
predictor here
will be reserved for only the branches
that actually need to go there because
the two bit predictor is not predicting
them correctly because pischer and
g-share have different strengths
and neither of them is clearly superior
to the other we are not going to combine
them using a hierarchical predictor
we are going to combine them using a
tournament predictor
that will choose between
p share
and g share
so the correct answer is that the
overall predictor is a hierarchical
predictor that chooses between a
two bit predictor and
a tournament predictor which itself
chooses between p-share and g-share or
the other way around